drbenkim.com 2019-09-02

# Terms of Use & Privacy Policy

The drbenkim.com User Agreement is the agreement between Dr. Ben Kim Natural Health Solutions Inc., and the drbenkim.com User (You).

Hereafter, Dr. Ben Kim Natural Health Solutions, Inc. will be referred to as "the Clinic."

You must be eighteen (18) years or older to access drbenkim.com. If you are under eighteeen years of age, you are not permitted to access drbenkim.com for any reason. Due to the age restrictions for use of this website, no information obtained by this website falls within the child online privacy act (COPA) and is not monitored as doing so.

You agree that Ontario law will govern this agreement, and that any claim or suit arising out of or related to this agreement must be brought exclusively in federal or provincial courts located in Barrie, Ontario. You consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of such courts.

You agree that in no event will the Clinic be liable to you for any special, incidental or consequential damages.

You agree to indemnify and hold the Clinic harmless for any damages or costs incurred as a result of your violation of any law, regardless of whether they are actual, incidental, consequential, or punitive.

You assume full responsibility for your decision to use the information available on drbenkim.com and its affiliated services. The Clinic offers information and services "as is" and disclaims any implied warranties including for merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and non-infringement.

You understand that the Clinic does not directly or indirectly dispense medical advice or prescribe the use of fasting or diet as a form of treatment for sickness without medical approval from your doctor. Nutritionists and other experts in the field of health and nutrition hold widely varying views.

You understand that the Clinic does not intend to diagnose or prescribe for you. You understand that the Clinic offers natural health information to help you cooperate with your doctor or other health practitioner in your mutual quest for a better life.

You understand that throughout this website, statements are made pertaining to the properties and/or functions of food and/or nutritional products. These statements have not been evaluated by the United States Food and Drug Administration and these materials and products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease.

You understand that if you use any information on drbenkim.com without your doctor's or health practitioner's approval, you prescribe for yourself, and this remains your legal right. The Clinic assumes no responsibility.

You understand that the Clinic reserves the right to modify the drbenkim.com User Agreement at any time.

Privacy Policy

The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

For example, you may need to provide the following information in placing an order at our catalogue:

• Name

• Email address and shipping address

• Home and business phone number

In addition to providing the foregoing information, if you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed and designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you always have the option to opt out of any such updates; simply contact us using our contact form, or use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of every newsletter that we send out.

**What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers.

Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We utilize encryption/security best practices to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

**Communication Opt Out**

If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from us, you can unsubscribe by following the opt-out instructions at the bottom of our newsletters, or if for some reason your e-mail program doesn't display an option to opt out, you can let us know via the contact form which you can find in our natural health shop. 

**Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?**

We do not share your information with anyone. Period. 

**What about Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein.
